Finding Aid for the John Kimmel Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
John Kimmel Collection
1845 - 1864
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0239
.07 linear feet
Scope and Contents
This collection contains 15 items. The letters are addressed primarily to John Kimmel from friends, during the Civil War. One letter is addressed to Lucy Ingham, who became his wife. There is one unidentified daguerreotype photograph included in the collection, and one poem by John Kimmel.
- Correspondence – to Lucy Ingham
  - October 25, 1845
- Correspondence – from Walter Norton Chapin
  - August 12, 1862
  - October, 1862
  - December 7, 1862
  - March 3, 1863
  - April 3, 1863
  - May 16, 1863
  - June 12, 1863
  - July 9, 1863
  - July 16, 1863
  - July 23, 1863
  - August 29, 1863
- Correspondence – from Stephen M. Kemp
  - July 2, 1864
- Correspondence – from T. B. W Stockton
  - September 12, 1860
- Poem
  - August 16, 1852
- Photograph
  - 1 daguerreotype – unidentified, n.d.